adfiver.com 2016-03-16

# AdFiver: Privacy Policy

Effective Date: October 10, 2015

AdFiver values your privacy in your personal information that you store in our Service.

This Privacy Policy explains what information we collect about you and why and what we may do with that information and how we handle your personal information.

1. Information Collection and Use

If you register for or maintain an AdFiver Account:

| We collect | Why we collect it  
---|---  
Your username, email address, birthday, location and IP address. |  1\. To communicate with you.

2\. To help you create an account.

3\. To show you relevant content in the website.

4\. To create and support your AdFiver account.

5\. To prevent unauthorized access.  
  
2. Information Access and Disclosure

AdFiver is not in the business of selling or renting your information. Outside of actions you take within the Service, we only disclose your information - and then only the minimum information necessary - when:

1\. We believe it is necessary to investigate potential violations of our Terms of Service, to enforce those Terms of Service, or where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent or take action regarding illegal activities or suspected fraud, property or the systems on which we operate the Service.

2\. We determine that the access, preservation or disclosure of information is required or permitted by law to protect the rights, property or personal safety of AdFiver and users of the Service, or is required to comply with applicable laws, including compliance with warrants, court orders or other legal process.

3. What Cookies Does AdFiver Use?

AdFiver uses cookies and similar technologies to assist with functions such as user authentication, remembering user preferences, understanding how users use our Service, and managing and tracking the effectiveness of our marketing efforts.

We also may include tracking pixels, which are small graphic images, in our email messages and newsletters to determine whether the messages were opened and the links were actually clicked. In some cases, as outlined below, third parties may also get the opportunity to set cookies.

4. Data Storage

Please be aware that Personal Information and Content submitted to AdFiver will be transferred to a data center in the United States. If you post information to the AdFiver sites you are confirming your consent to such information, including Personal Information and Content, being transmitted to, hosted and accessed in the United States.
